faceitapps.com 2016-03-14

# Apps-O-Rama | Privacy

Effective Date: February 15, 2014

* * *

### Introduction

Face It Applications LLC d/b/a Apps-O-Rama and its subsidiaries (collectively, "AoR") recognize that its customers, visitors, users, and others (collectively or individually "Users") who use games, applications, and other services hosted by AoR (collectively, the "AoR Sites") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the AoR Sites. AoR provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the AoR Sites.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the AoR Terms of Use. Your use of the AoR Sites and any personal information you provide on the AoR Sites remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you access the AoR Sites from a third-party social networking site, you may also be required to read and accept the third party's Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

### THE INFORMATION AOR COLLECTS

 _User Provided Information through Facebook_

AoR's primary objective in collecting user information is to provide and enhance the AoR Sites and to enable users to easily navigate and enjoy the AoR Sites. When you use the AoR Sites, we may collect and record the information you provide us voluntarily through www.facebook.com ("Facebook") in accordance with the policies and terms of Facebook.

The types of personal information collected may vary depending on the activity. This "Personal Information" is defined as information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. Personal information may include: (1) your name (2) Facebook® user identification number, (3) email address, (4) physical address(es), and (5) phone number(s). Additionally, we may acquire information from you through (1) your access and participation in message boards on the AoR Sites, (2) your email of a question to our customer support, or (3) your purchase of a product. We may also collect (1) certain technical information about your mobile device or computer system, including MAC Address, IP Address and mobile device ID; and (2) usage statistics about your interactions with the AoR Sites.

Personal Information, for purposes of this Privacy Policy, will not include (1) game play information, such as stored game data, high scores, or game session duration, (2) any image, video, or other content posted by you on the AoR Sites, or (3) any information you may choose to share about yourself throughout the AoR Sites, such as in games or on message boards. Any actions you perform with other players are considered public and at your sole discretion.

 _User Provided Information through Prize Redemption_

In the event that you wish to claim a prize won through one of AoR's rewards-based gaming applications, you will need to follow certain procedures set forth in the terms of such application. Some of these procedures may include the submission of certain Personal Information, such as your photo identification. Such Personal Information is used only to verify your eligibility in the sweepstakes.

 _Advertiser, Publisher, or Developer Provided Information_

If you sign up as an advertiser, publisher, or developer, you will provide your name, company name and email address. We use this information to set up your account and allow you to place ads on our site. For developers, we allow you to create ad placement tags and embed ad tags into application code. When we deem it necessary to do so, we may send you service related announcements, such as to inform you that our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance.

 _Cookies Information_

When you visit the AoR Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. AoR uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the AoR Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our sites.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, or tracking utility company is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access to or control of these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, or tracking utility company use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

 _Log File Information_

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. When you register with or visit the AoR Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser provides. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order in which those pages were viewed, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

 _Clear Gifs Information_

When you use the AoR Sites, AoR or a third party advertising partner may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your AoR account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our Users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make AoR Sites better for our Users.

 _Flash LSOs_

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences, such as volume control or high game score, or to display content to personalize your visit based upon what you view on our site. Third parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118>.

 _Resume Submission_

If you choose to submit a resume to AoR via our site, please be aware that the resume submission may be hosted on a third party service provider's platform. Nevertheless, all personal information is stored and the upload of your resume is done by AoR. Our Privacy Policy governs the collection and use of this information. We use this information for the sole purpose of contacting you regarding the job for which you have applied.

### THE WAY AOR USES INFORMATION

If you submit personally identifiable information to us by use of the AoR Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide you the features and functionality of the AoR Sites.

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others to send you unsolicited messages. AoR is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these public areas of the site. Your display name (not your email address) may be displayed to other Users when you upload images or videos or send messages through the AoR Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any images, captions, videos or other content that you submit to the AoR Sites may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

We may use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major AoR Site changes, new messages in your inbox, for customer service purposes, or if you are a potential winner in a sweepstakes). We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the AoR Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.  
We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) retain information so that you will not be required to re-enter it during your visits to the AoR Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics, including total number of visitors and traffic; (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests; (f) diagnose or fix technical problems reported by Users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (g) access your information after you sign in.

### WHEN AOR DISCLOSES INFORMATION

AoR will not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information other than as described in this privacy policy.

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf, including credit card processing. We require that our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy and we use reasonable efforts, including confidentiality and security measures, to limit their use of such information.

We use a third party payment gateway. If you choose to make a purchase within one of our applications, you will be transferred to a third party payment gateway to make the payment. The third party then provides AoR the name on the account and the amount paid so that we may complete the transaction.

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the AoR Site. AoR may share personally-identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information with third party-affiliates and business partners for the purpose of offering greater functionality and enhanced services through AoR or other sites, and for the purpose of communicating these services to you.

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including but not limited to, fraud, potential threats to public safety or the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise permitted by law.

AoR also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information that AoR believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our the AoR Sites, and to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of AoR, our Users or others.

### YOUR CHOICES

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the AoR Sites, in which case AoR may not be able to provide certain services to you. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the AoR Sites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions or comments about security on our Web site or this Privacy Policy, you can email us at [info@appsorama.com](mailto:info@appsorama.com).

### THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS, LINKS TO OTHER SITES

AoR allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the AoR Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the AoR Sites. These third-parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

AoR does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks AoR to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the target audience.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

AoR uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to AoR and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, AoR makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If AoR learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective measures. AoR may post a notice on the AoR Sites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us by using the contact Information in this statement.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to AoR. For that reason, AoR does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the AoR Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the AoR Sites at any time or in any manner. If AoR learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the AoR Sites then AoR will take the appropriate steps to delete this information immediately.

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents or guardians for permission before sending any personal information to anyone over the Internet.

### INTERNATIONAL USERS

The AoR Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the AoR Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from the laws of the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of the AoR Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

### ACCESS TO AND MANAGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

 _General_

We believe it is important for you to be able to find out what personally identifiable information you have provided to us through the AoR Sites. If you have provided us with personally identifiable information, you can contact us to request that we provide you with the personally identifiable information we have in our records about you. We reserve the right to limit the number of times such a request can be made and to charge you for responding to such requests if this process is misused or abused.

If you become aware that personally identifiable information or sensitive information you may have provided that we have in our records about you is inaccurate, incomplete, or incompatible with the purposes for which it was provided or subsequently authorized by you, please notify us using the contact information provided below. To inquire about your personally identifiable or sensitive information, and to correct, amend, or delete such information, please send a request by email with your current contact information to [info@appsorama.com](mailto:info@appsorama.com).

 _California Users_

We do not share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure, typically by "opting in" to receive information from a third party that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of the AoR Sites. If you do ask us to share your personal information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific promotion, as we do not share information with any third party (other than our service providers) on a continual basis. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personal information on one of our sites.

Users in certain jurisdictions have a right to access personal information held about them. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with applicable law. Please submit any requests for access to your personal data in writing to [info@appsorama.com](mailto:info@appsorama.com).

### IN THE EVENT OF MERGER, SALE, OR BANKRUPTCY

In the event that AoR undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer all of your information, including personal information, to the successor organization in such a transition. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

### CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page frequently to become aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the AoR Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

If we change how we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Date Last Modified: This Privacy Policy was last modified February 15, 2014.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have questions about this Policy, please contact AoR.  
Apps-O-Rama  
1849 Geary Blvd.  
P.O. Box 156461  
San Francisco, CA 94115  
You may email questions to [info@appsorama.com](mailto:info@appsorama.com).

### HELPFUL LINKS
